

ABOUT ME

I am a trained Electrical engineer in the field of Telecommunications with more than 10 years of professional experience in various technical fields. I was constantly able to fulfil my work on time and to adhere to very high quality standards. In 2019, I decided to switch my career path to embrace programming, which always used to be my goal, by joining a full stack web development course at DCI based on the MERN Stack. I am looking forward to applying my work ethic and analytic abilities that I developed in my career in the field of web development.

SKILLS

Technologies:

JavaScript

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Node.js

Databases:

- MongoDB
- Mongoose
- MySQL
- **Version Control:**

JavaScript

¡Query

Bootstrap

Frameworks:

React - Redux

- Git
- GitHub

English (C1) German (B2)

Serbian Croatian

CONTACT -

- Hamburg
- +49 174 623 15 25
- alen.eftimov@gmail.com
- https://github.com/Alen-Eftimov
- in www.linkedin.com/in/eftimov-alen
- https://www.xing.com/profile /Alen_Eftimov3/cv

Alen Eftimov

Full Stack Web Developer

EDUCATION

2019 - 2021 🖕 Full Stack Web Developer

DCI Hamburg - DigitalCareerInstitute gGmbH

- Accomplishing a one-year-full-time training including technologies from MERN stack
- Completing multiple small and one large practical project to practise

1995 - 2006 M.Sc. in Electrical and Telecommunications Engineering Faculty of Electronic Engineering Niš - University of Niš, Serbia

EXPERIENCE -

2014 - 2017 o Independent Designer of Telecommunication Systems -Belgrade, Serbia

- **Designing:** video surveillance, alarm systems, fire alarm, sound system, computer, telephone and optical network for buildings, shops and houses.
- Technologies used: AutoCad, MS Office

2013 - 2014 💍

CEG International - Doha, Qatar

- Consultant of Telecommunications Systems for : video surveillance, alarm systems, fire alarm, sound system, computer, telephone and optical network.
- Technologies used: AutoCad, MS Office

2007 - 2013

ARHIPRO - Belgrade, Serbia

- Designer of telecommunication Systems for : video surveillance, alarm systems, fire alarm, sound system, computer, telephone and optical networks in buildings, shops and houses.
- Technologies used: AutoCad, MS Office

RELEVANT PROJECTS -

Dr.House

https://dr-house.herokuapp.com

- Multi-purpose health care website for hospitals, clinics, doctors and patients.
- Technologies used: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, EJS, Bootstrap, MongoDB

EXPERTISE -

HOBBIES & INTERESTS -

Web development Responsive design

Clean coding

Database systems

Code testing

Effective writing

Reading **Traveling** Jogging